FRANCISCO ALEXANDRE PINTO NEVES

 3^{rd} year Software Engineering Student at Universidade do Minho in Braga, Portugal



CONTACT

franeves08@gmail.com

+351 935 759 873

Viana do Castelo, Portugal

@franl08

Francisco Neves

SKILLS

Python Java C C# **SQL** LaTeX Git **Prolog** Haskell HTML/CSS Markdown

Operating Systems

Unix Windows Software & Tools

Office MySQL Adobe

(e.g. Photoshop, Premiere, ...)

Languages

Portuguese Spanish English French German

STRENGTHS

Motivated Fast learner Team worker Sociable Hard worker Good leader Quick thinker

HOBBIES

Reading **Painting** Running **Watching Sports** Listening to Music

ABOUT ME

I'm a 20 year old (25-09-2001, Porto) software engineering student at Universidade do Minho in Braga, Portugal.

Currently, I'm on the third year of my bachelors degree, but I'm planning on getting a master's degree after I finish my graduation.

I'm looking for an internship for the 2022 summer in order to get some experience in the world of development and learn new things.

EXPERIENCE

🛗 2015 - 2022 (part time)

Football Referee Associação de Futebol

de Viana do Castelo

Developed soft skills and learned to deal with pressure while doing my job.

🛗 2020 – 2021 (summer part time)

Waiter Poço Bar

V.N. Cerveira

Worked with clients of all kind and dealed with pressure to execute my work in the fastest time possible.

🛗 jul 2019 – set 2019 (summer part time)

Receptionist Aguamuseu do Rio Minho

V.N. Cerveira

Worked with clients of all kind, organized the museum bibliography and created a file on Excel to control the work flow and prices.

NON PROFIT

Universidade do Minho

Marketing Department Collaborator CeSIUM

oct 2021 - feb 2022

Marketing Team Member SEI Universidade do Minho

2016 - 2019 Team Member

Parlamento dos Jovens V.N. Cerveira

2018

Organizer Cerveira Abraça a Terra

EDUCATION

2019 -**Bachelors on Software Engineering** Universidade do Minho

1 2012 - 2019 **Basic and Middle Education**

Escola Básica e Secundária V.N. Cerveira

Finished Middle Education in Sciences and Technologies with an average of 17.2. On the last year, I had as optional subjects Chemistry and Informatic Applications. Obtained a diploma of merit in every year, except 9th.

PROJECTS

Braga

yet another PreProcessor **Green Distribution** Sports Manager